<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Takahiro Suzuki Personal Blog</title>
    <link>https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Takahiro Suzuki Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to deploy a static web site to GitHub pages</title>
      <link>https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/how_to_deploy_gh_pg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/how_to_deploy_gh_pg/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone🤩! This post will show you how to deploy your static site to GitHub pages. In the last post, I introduced you to how to deploy HUGO&amp;rsquo;s static website to Amazon S3, but one of the consciousness must be the price. As far as a free tier, S3 will provide 5G in standard S3 storage, 20,000 GET/mon, and 2,000 PUT/mon. It would be charitable, and generous service, but you might still worry about if you should check out, specifically student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Website hosting on AWS S3 ~ Part I ~</title>
      <link>https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/static_web_site_hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/static_web_site_hosting/</guid>
      <description>Hello Coder🤩! Welcome to my personal blog! This is my first post. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna introduce you to the architecture behind this blog, and I would like to show you how easy to create personal blog with HUGO, and how to deploy your static site to AWS S3 based on the best practice.
HUGO   Recently, a lot of static site generator is available for free, like Nuxt.js, GatsbyJS, HUGO, NEXT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Website hosting on AWS S3 ~ Part II ~</title>
      <link>https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/static_web_site_hosting_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://funabashi800.github.io/blog/static_web_site_hosting_2/</guid>
      <description>Hello Coder🤩! Welcome to my personal blog! This post will show you how to deploy HUGO static site from GitHub to AWS S3 automatically via TravisCI.
Create S3 Bucket First of all, let&amp;rsquo;s make an S3 bucket to host static site, but before that, you need IAM account which has a managed permission to S3 because you have to need to deploy some files via TravisCI programmatically.
  Static Website Hosting     Public Access Control   After creating a S3 bucket allowed for public access, you need to attach some policy to the S3 bucket, because you are going to upload multiple file to S3 bucket programmatically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>